Contact

0488 076 807 (Mobile) martyna@adminflow.com.au

www.linkedin.com/in/martynakrawczyk-920448a2 (LinkedIn) adminflow.com.au (Company)

Top Skills

Customer Service
Office Administration
Microsoft Office

Languages

Polish (Limited Working)

Certifications

FieldInsight Certified Partner ServiceM8 Certified Partner Receipt Bank Partner Zapier Certified Expert Introduction to HTML

Martyna Krawczyk

Protégé Developer at MYOB, student at Coder Academy and consultant at Adminflow.

Melbourne, Australia

Summary

An experienced SME innovator that marries technology with systems and processes, combined with passion and commitment, to be your partner in getting back to what's important to you.

I bring a wealth of experience in business operations, finance, project management, stakeholder relationship building and business planning and development, tailoring it to your specific business needs.

Trades and Professional Services are my specialty and I relish working with you to describe your end state before developing a holistic end to end solution to ensure your business outcomes are met. I'm excited by the things you may not be - systems and processes matched to the right technology are the skills I bring to the table with a focus on enhancing the customer experience and client usability.

Experience

MYOB

Protégé Developer August 2019 - Present

The Future Maker's Academy is our program for bringing people from diverse backgrounds together to create great software.

It provides a solid foundation to those new in their career on the things we value most in making software at MYOB. Participants learn by doing, working collaboratively with others under the guide of their mentors.

The academy is not just about writing code, it's about having a growth mindset, it's about team work, it's about learning our culture.

Adminflow
Director
August 2017 - Present
Melbourne, Australia

Adminflow develops and implements time-saving strategies for small to medium businesses, with a focus on administration workflows and the customer experience.

Our clients use us because they keep the human interaction while using technology as the efficiency tool.

Supporting You Virtual Administration
Principal Consultant
October 2014 - August 2017 (2 years 11 months)
Melbourne, Australia

Results-focussed Online Business Managers with a passion for:

Talking to and working with inspirational entrepreneurs

Administrative and Financial Management (Bookkeeping, Payroll and BAS Lodgement)

Development and Implementation of Workplace Systems and Processes (Continuous Improvement)

Design and Formulation of Workplace Manuals

Ongoing Research and Analysis of new Methods and Technologies

Human Resource Management and Staff Training

Development of Marketing Material, incl. Newsletters, Blogs and Social Media Content.

Thompson May Commercial
Assistant Property Manager and Sales Secretary
November 2015 - June 2016 (8 months)

Accepted the invitation to join the team responsible for managing a commercial property portfolio (offices, retail and industrial rentals). Additional responsibilities necessitate supervision of one Trust Account Administrator; website management and handling of online marketing issues; organising scheduled and preventative maintenance; overseeing financial reporting and general accounting functions. In short, the main contact for all property management and sales & leasing administration matters.

1300 Driveways
Office Manager / PA to Project Manager

2008 - 2015 (8 years)

Melbourne, Australia

This was a diverse, time sensitive and multi-disciplinary position, with a high client service emphasis, where the primary objective was to provide administrative support on, between 30 to 40 landscaping projects, at any one time (project duration times anywhere up to three weeks); handle all client liaison (Government departments and agencies, builders, property developers and general public); manage the accounting functions and all HR issues including staff selection and recruitment of apprentices and landscapers.

1300 DRIVEWAYS was established in 2008. The Company built a good reputation for quality craftsmanship and was subsequently nominated for the Industry's 'LIAV Rising Star Award 2010'.

- Extensive interaction and communication with management, clients, staff, engineers, surveyors, Local Councils and suppliers
- Maintaining a comprehensive knowledge of the Concreting and Landscaping Industry, along with contemporary business practices, methods of operation, OH&S and compliance issues and ongoing technological advancements
- Management of human resource functions for apprentices and arranging appropriate training (first aid certificates, special licences...)
- Continuous improvement of all systems and processes
- Administrative management of various reporting and recording activities;
 bookings, quotes, general enquiries, diary management and secretarial functions, equipment control and general accounting

Education

Coder Academy

Diploma of Information Technology, Information Technology (2019 - 2020)

Chisholm Institute

Diploma of Accounting, Accounting and Finance (2016 - 2019)

RMIT University

Certificate III in Real Estate (Agents' Representative)

Box Hill Institute
Certificate IV Animal Technology